(Bernadette:)No.
(Sheldon:)I'm glad because I would not
have seen that coming.
(Raj:)Amy, I could use some help.
(Amy:)Let me guess. There's an undergrad
in a leather jacket
(Amy:)snapping his fingers
by the water fountain.
(Raj:)I thought about
what you said last night,
(Raj:)and I went back
on the dating website
and I was locking
at this girl's profile.
(Raj:)She's amazing.
(Amy:)Oh, she's cute.
(Amy:)And smart. Phi Beta Kappa.
(Raj:)And judging by her lack
of Adam's apple,
(Raj:)she's been female her entire life.
(Raj:)I like that in a woman.
(Howard:)Great,
so what do you need me for?
(Raj:)Well, I was up all night trying
to write to her,
(Raj:)but I wanted to run it by
you first.
(Amy:)-All right.
"Emily,
(Raj:)your face is like
a precious dew-kissed flower."
(Amy:)Wow.
(Raj:)I know.
Powerful stuff, huh?